Seino!
Nighttime and Idols
Hello everyone, I'm Ayaho Takaichi.
I'm Tomoko Hazuki
I'm Aoho Mori.
Today let's talk about Tokyo Nighttime Land vol. 4, which will be going live soon!
Here's what the former looks like
Gorgeous!
Do you want to get to know each other or are you good friends with this person?
I'm not sure, but I've met Yuzuki Daikoku, the orca, and she's been very kind to me, even taking me out to dinner,
But it's been a long time since we last met, so it's been a while since we last saw each other,
I was a little nervous.
I was a little nervous because I hadn't seen you for a long time.
It's been a long time since I've seen you all,
I was also a part of this nighttime land,
When it was announced, I got a call from Hanana Sakamoto of SHACHI,
She said we would be together next time and that she was looking forward to it. She said we should definitely have a Bonjiri meeting after the rehearsal.
Bonjiri?
The only thing we have in common is that we like Bonjiri, and since it's not easy to find people who like Bonjiri, my Bonjiri friend contacted me.
So, a Bonjiri friend of mine contacted me.
Is there anyone?
I'm a bit shy myself, so I haven't talked to any of them,
But the other day, I had a chance to go home with Mr. Kitami from Tohoku-san after Keikou,
She is very talkative and cute,
I would like to be friends with her.
I'd like to be friends with her.
I wonder if he's watching?
But you know, Emma Yuna, too, But, you know, Emayuna, too,
I just met her for the first time,
She's so cute, so cute, so cute,
I felt like hugging her.
You know, really.
She was like an angel.
But they are really cute, the two of them.
This performance brought out a new side of them that I hadn't seen before,
I had not seen it before, so I think it's great.
Yes, I agree.
But they are cute.
That's cute.
It's a little bit floating.
Physically.
I think it floats a little.
Because it was too cute to float. I'm sure. Like an angel.
She was really picking on him today. She was so cute.
Don't go too far. They will hear you.
I'm sure we'll get to know each other well from now on, so let's do our best. I'll do my best.
But we have already started training, you know. It's started.
How do you see it?
This is a period drama, Shinsengumi, so it is not only a play, but also a shield,
It is not the first time for me to play the shield,
It is not the first time for me to play a shield, but since I will be playing a member of the Shinsengumi, the shield is only a part of the play, not a battle.
I thought it would be difficult for me not to fight as myself, because I would be fighting as myself.
The gender also changes when you play a male role, doesn't it?
Yes.
I wonder. I wonder, what is it?
I don't know, the tempo is kind of difficult.
It's a work with great comedic elements,
I thought it was difficult to find a good sense of rhythm, or to connect well with the audience.
I thought it was very difficult to connect them well.
I think tempo is important in comedies.
There are so many points where you want to make the audience laugh.
I'm nervous about that.
But I want people to laugh somehow.
But there are comedic elements in it,
But while there are comedic elements, the growth of the new members is also a highlight, so I hope you enjoy it.
Also, there may or may not be singing and dancing in the play.
Sometimes there is singing and dancing, and sometimes there is not.
Sometimes there is, sometimes there isn't. Well, there is singing and dancing,
Well, it has been a long time since I sang and danced.
Yes, it has been a long time since I sang and danced.
I think this is one of the characteristics of the nighttime land,
I'm sure there will be many songs that everyone knows, and there may be songs in the show that everyone can get excited about.
There are many things to look forward to. There are a lot of songs to look forward to.
There are a lot of cute girls. I'm looking forward to it.
I'm anxious to see the reaction. Yes, I am.
So when you first got this job, what did you think when you heard about it?
I'm going to be in it.
I don't know. I didn't know about this nighttime land,
What? What is Tokyo Night Land? What is nighttime? I still don't know much about it,
I still don't understand it very well,
Maybe there is no right answer to the question of what nighttime is.
No! I thought, "Is this how it's supposed to be? I thought, "This is what it's like," but then I heard that it was a play, No! Is this how it's supposed to be? But when I heard it was a play, I thought it was amazing,
I thought it was great, but then I heard it was a play, and I thought, well, you know, Third Planet is an idol division,
What? They do theater too? I was so surprised,
I was surprised and thought that Stardust is indeed a great company.
But I thought it was something new and fresh,
I was surprised when I saw the members,
I thought I would take my first step and see what it was all about,
So I accepted the offer.
I was thinking that the rumpus is like this,
I've been performing in the nighttime land,
Yes, Nairuna-chan, Loompumpa was listening to a lot of stories,
I was thinking that the volume 1, 2, and 3 are quite different each time,
This time, I really had a lot of fun,
This time, it's really a play, a period drama,
This time, it's really a play, and a period drama, which is a complete change from the last time,
I am going to do this play,
I think there are many things I can learn from it,
I think I have a lot to learn from this play,
I think I will be able to learn a lot from this experience, and I also feel that I will be able to learn a lot from it,
I think it will be a rare opportunity for me to perform with the children of STAPLA,
I think it would be very rare to have such an experience,
I'm really excited about every single rehearsal,
I'm looking forward to it.
When I heard about it,
I didn't know about it,
I looked it up a lot, and found it on YouTube and watched it,
I watched the last "Rose of Versailles," right? I thought it looked interesting, and it had a strong comedic element,I saw the last "Rose of Versailles," right? I thought it looked interesting and had a strong comedic element,
I'm not really good at comedies, so I thought I'd like to try my hand at acting.
When I saw your name, you contacted me in the first place, even before I had decided on the job,
I felt very safe. I was very happy to be able to work with her, and when I saw her name, I knew I wanted to work with her, so I was really looking forward to rehearsing with her.
She is cute. I was watching her from next to me, and she was so cute.
You say that so suddenly.
But you know, this is the first time we've worked together like this, so I'm very happy. I'm very happy to be given such an opportunity.
I'm very grateful.
Thank you, Yakan-kun.
Not at all for being in the middle of the show.
So, let's review Tokyo Night Land Vol. 4.
Tokyo Nighttime Land Vol. 4, Shinseigumi Bakumatsu Night Tour, will be held on Tuesday, December 5 at Kanda Square Hall.
There will be two performances, a daytime performance at 3:00 p.m. and a nighttime performance at 7:00 p.m.
There will be two performances, one at 3:00 p.m. and the other at 7:00 p.m. Tickets for the noon performance are still available.
So please come and see us!
We are looking forward to seeing you!
Now let's hear your enthusiasm from Chi-chan.
Well, I will be playing the role of Mr. Harada, a member of the Shinsengumi, the new generation of the Shinsengumi.
I don't know how to put it, even in a period piece.
I have assisted the older members in the past, but this is my first time to play a role that I can show to everyone.
But this is the first time for me to play a role that I'm going to present to you all.
I hope it will be a great challenge for me to play the role of a man.
Above all, I hope I can bring a lot of laughter to the theater.
The stage is a living thing, so please come and see it with your own eyes.
I would be very happy if you could come and see it with your own eyes. I look forward to seeing you. I will do my best.
The part I play is in the play, and I work, but there is no description in the synopsis, so I am looking forward to seeing what kind of role I will play in the play.
I am sure some of you will be seeing me in a play for the first time, so I hope you will enjoy it.
I will do my best to make them think that this actress is very nice. I will do my best to make you think that this actress is very nice.
I will do my best. I will do my best.
I play the role of Oyo, and I'm not even in the synopsis yet.
What kind of role will I play and will I have anything to do with the two guys from 3B?
Will they fight?
I hope that you will pay attention to what I have to say.
So, let's work hard in rehearsals starting tomorrow!
That's it for this three-part series.
See you next time at Tokyo Night Land!
So far, my partners have been Hoto Koichi, aka Tomo Tsukimoto, and Abo Mori.
Bye bye!